techstreet.com 2016-12-20

# Privacy Policy & Practices

Your privacy is important to Techstreet, a Thomson Reuters business, and we go to great lengths to protect it. This Privacy Statement applies to the online collection of personal information via websites and mobile applications operated by Techstreet, a Thomson Reuters business, and its worldwide affiliated companies and subsidiaries. This Statement does not apply to information collected in any other way, including offline. 

Our website may contain links to sites maintained by others. This Privacy Statement does not reflect the privacy practices of those sites. 

### Techstreet Privacy Statement - Highlights

This statement applies to the online collection of personal information via websites operated by Techstreet, a Thomson Reuters business, and its worldwide affiliated companies and subsidiaries. Highlights of the Online Privacy Statement follow immediately below, or read the 

Full Text. 

### What personal information is collected and how is that information used?

  * We collect information about our users in three ways: directly from the user (such as when ordering a product, registering an account or signing up for a newsletter), from our Web server logs, and through cookies. 
  * We use the information primarily to provide you with a personalized Internet experience that delivers the information, resources, and services that are most relevant and helpful to you. 
  * We do not share any of the information you provide with others, unless we say so in this Privacy Statement, or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. 

More Details

### How is my personal information protected?

  * We have implemented certain appropriate security measure to help protect your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. 
  * However, please note that we cannot guarantee that unauthorized persons will always be unable to defeat our security measures. 
  * Also, please note that we may store and process your personal information in systems located outside of your home country. Regardless of where these activities occur, we take appropriate steps to ensure that your information is protected consistent with the principles set forth under this Privacy Statement. 

More Details

### Who has access to the personal information?

  * We will not sell, rent, or lease mailing lists or other customer data to others, and we will not make your personal information available to any unaffiliated parties, except our approved agents and contractors, or as otherwise described in this Privacy Statement. 
  * We rely on some of our affiliates for support of the products and services we offer, and we share some of our back-office functions with other Thomson Reuters companies. Our affiliates are all required to preserve the confidentiality of any personal information they may access. 
  * We will not disclose any personal information or information about your usage of our websites to unaffiliated third parties, except as necessary to service the account, to enforce the terms of use, to meet our obligations to content and technology providers, or as required by law. 

More Details

### How may I correct, amend or delete my personal information, or update my preferences?

  * You may update your preferences at any time on the Communication Preferences page, accessible [here](http://www.techstreet.com/account/users/edit)
  * If you do not want to receive information about our products or services, please update your account preferences (where available), check the appropriate box when registering and/or utilize the "unsubscribe" mechanism within the communications that you receive from us. 
  * If you have any additional questions or concerns related to this statement and/or our practices, please contact us via email at [techstreet.service@thomsonreuters.com](mailto:techstreet.service@thomsonreuters.com) or via phone at 1-734-780-8000. 

More Details

Back To Top

### SCOPE

Your privacy is important to Techstreet, a Thomson Reuters Business. In this Privacy Statement, you can learn what kind of information we collect, when and how we might use that information, how we protect the information, who has access to it, and what choices you have with respect to your personal information. 

This Privacy Statement applies only to information collected online from the users of this website. Unless expressly stated, this Privacy Statement does not apply to any other Thomson Reuters website and does not apply to information we may collect in any other way, including offline. 

Our website may contain links to sites maintained by others. This Privacy Statement does not reflect the privacy practices of those sites and if you have any questions about the privacy practices associated with those sites, please review the privacy statement posted on each site. 

__Please read this Privacy Statement in its entirety to understand the following:__   

### WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DOES THOMSON REUTERS COLLECT AND HOW DOES IT USE THAT INFORMATION?

We collect information about our users in three ways: directly from the user, from our Web server logs, and through cookies. We use the information primarily to provide you with a personalized Internet experience that delivers the information, resources, and services that are most relevant and helpful to you. We don't share any of the information you provide with others, unless we say so in this Privacy Statement, or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. 

_User-Supplied Information_

: When you register for our services or order products via our site, we ask you to provide some personal information 9such as your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, payment card information and/or certain additional categories of information resulting from use of our websites and services, such as research requests). We keep this information in a contact data base for future reference, as needed. We may use certain information you provide to offer you products and services that we believe may be of interest to you. If you don't wish to receive such offers, you may opt out (unsubscribe) as described below. 

If you contact us for customer support, we may ask you to provide information about your computer or about the issues you are trying to resolve. This information is necessary to help us answer your questions. We may record your requests and our responses for quality control purposes. 

_Web server logs_

: When you visit our website, we may track information about your visit and store that information in web server logs, which are records of activities on our sites. Our servers automatically capture and save the information electronically. Examples of the information we may collect include: 

  * your unique Internet protocol address; 
  * the name of your unique Internet service provider; 
  * the city, state, and country from which you access or website; 
  * the kind of browser or computer you use; 
  * the number of links you click within the site; 
  * the date and time of your visit; 
  * the web page from which you arrived to our site; 
  * the pages you viewed on the site; and 
  * certain searches/queries that you conducted via our website(s). 

The information we collect in web server logs helps us administer the site, analyze its usage, protect the website and its content from inappropriate use and improve the user's experience. 

_Cookies_

: In order to offer and provide a customized and personal service, we may use cookies to store and help track information about you. Cookies are simply small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to help remind us who you are and to help you navigate our sites during your visits. Cookies allow us to save passwords and preferences for you so you won't have to re-enter them each time you visit. 

The use of cookies is relatively standard. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. However, if you prefer, you can set your browser to either notify you when you receive a cookie, or to refuse to accept cookies. You should understand that some features of many sites may not function properly if you don't accept cookies. 

Back To Top

### HOW DOES TECHSTREET PROTECT THE PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT IT COLLECTS?

We have implemented certain appropriate security measures to help protect your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, some of our websites are protected with Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. Also, we store the information about you in a date center with restricted access and appropriate monitoring and we use a variety of technical security measures to secure your data. In addition, we use intrusion detection and virus protection software. However, please note that we cannot guarantee that unauthorized persons will always be unable to defeat our security measures. 

Also, please note that we may store and process your personal information in systems located outside of your home country. However, regardless of where these activities occur, we take appropriate steps to ensure that your information is protected consistent with the principles set forth under this statement. 

Back To Top

### WHO HAS ACCESS TO THE INFORMATION?

We will not sell, rent, or lease mailing lists or other customer data to others, and we will not make your personal information available to any unaffiliated parties, except as follows: 

  * to agents and/or contractors who may use it on our behalf or in connection with their relationship with us (for example, we may use third parties to help us with promotional campaigns); and 
  * as required by law, in a matter of public safety or policy, as needed in connection with the transfer or our business assets (for example, if we are acquired by another company or if we are liquidated during bankruptcy proceedings), or if we believe in good faith that sharing the data is necessary to protect our rights or property. 

We also rely on some of our affiliates for support of the products and services we offer, and we share some of our back-office functions with other Thomson Reuters companies. Our affiliates are all required to preserve the confidentiality of any personal information they may access. 

We will not disclose any information about your usage to unaffiliated third parties, except as necessary to service the account, to enforce the terms of use, to meet our obligations to content and technology providers, or as required by law. 

We may also use statistics regarding usage for product development purposes, but we only use those statistics in the aggregate and they don't include any personally identifiable information about individual users. 

Your access to some of our services and content may be password protected. We recommend that you refrain from disclosing your username(s) and password(s) to anyone. We also recommend that you sign out of your account or service at the end of each session. You may also wish to close your browser window when you have finished your work, especially if you share a computer with someone else or if you are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe. 

Back To Top

### HOW MAY I CORRECT, AMEND OR DELETE MY PERSONAL INFORMATION AND/OR UPDATE MY PREFERENCES?

  * You may update your preferences at any time on the Communications Preferences page, accessible [here](http://www.techstreet.com/account/users/edit). 

If you have any additional questions or concerns related to this statement and/or our practices, please contact us via the following 

Address: 6300 Interfirst Dr.  
Ann Arbor, MI 48108  
Phone: 1-734-780-8000  
E-Mail: [techstreet.service@thomsonreuters.com](mailto:techstreet.service@thomsonreuters.com)

### PRIVACY STATEMENT CHANGES

If our information practices change in a significant way, we will post the policy changes here. This Privacy Statement was last updated on April 7, 2011. 

Back To Top
